等一下还会有下一班车的
There'll be another one along shortly.
现在因为我成了足球明星和战争英雄
Now, because I had been a football star and war hero
以及全国知名的人物和捕虾船的船长
and national celebrity and a shrimping boat captain
以及大学毕业生
and a college graduate,
亚拉巴马州绿茵镇的父老乡亲
the city fathers of Greenbow, Alabama,
决定给我一个好工作
decided to get together and offered me a fine job.
所以我不再回去和丹中尉一起工作了
So I never went back to work for Lieutenant Dan,
但他继续打理着我们布巴甘公司的财产
though he did take care of my Bubba Gump money.
他替我买了一家卖苹果的公司的股票
He got me invested in some kind of fruit company.
后有他打电话给我
So then I got a call from him
说我们再也不用担心没钱花了
saying we don't have to worry about money no more,
我说：“好啊 又少一件麻烦事”
and I said, "That's good. One less thing."
“我有了新的希望…”
# I've got a new hope... #
妈妈说过财产不用太多
Now Mama said there's only so much fortune
一个人用不了多少
a man really needs,